我曾是吸血鬼军团的精兵
I was an elite soldier in the vampire army.
死神使者
A Death Dealer.
我当时所向披靡
And I was good at it.
但我遭人背叛
But I was betrayed.
维克托 我所效忠的领袖 帝国最有权势之人…
Viktor, our leader and the most powerful vampire...
却并非我一心追随的救世主
...was not the saviour he had led me to believe.
一夜之间 盟友变为仇敌
Suddenly, allies turned enemies.
我曾誓死守卫的吸血鬼长老们 不肯让我活命
The vampire Elders I had once protected wanted me dead.
后来我遇到了迈克尔·柯文
Then I found Michael Corvin.
他身上既流着吸血鬼的血 也流着狼人的血
Neither vampire nor Lycan, Michael became a hybrid.
我们一起复仇 杀了那些长老
We retaliated, killed the Elders.
但一切随之天翻地覆
But then everything changed.
我被俘获 当时并不知晓自己已经怀了迈克尔的孩子
I was captured, not knowing that I was carrying Michael's child.
伊芙 我们的女儿 第一个纯种的混血儿…
Eve, our daughter, the first pure-blood hybrid...
因为她的血可以结束战争…
...whose blood could end the war...
受到吸血鬼和狼人的觊觎
...became highly sought after by both vampires and Lycans alike.
我只能把她藏起来 让自己与世人都不知她的去向…
My only choice was to hide her from the world and from myself...
这样即便是我也不能带人找到她
...so not even I could lead them to her.
我曾是吸血鬼军队的精兵
I was an elite soldier in the vampire army.
我只能把她藏起来 让自己与世人都不知她的去向…
My only choice was to hide her from the world...
这样即便是我也不能带人找到她
...so not even I could lead them to her.
《黑夜传说5：血战》
我已活了许久
I have lived beyond my time.
一千年后的新月对我来说…
Another new moon in 1000 years of new moons...
毫无意义
...and I do not care to see it.
我一无所有
I have nothing.
我的族人…
My coven...
我女儿…
...my daughter...
- 我所爱之人都离我而去 - 杀了她
- ...my love, all gone. - Cut her off!
也许不久后…
And soon, perhaps...
我也会灰飞烟灭
...my very existence.
- 赛琳来了 - 我同时被吸血鬼和狼人追杀
- Selene's coming! - I am hunted by vampires and Lycans.
现在我逃亡在外 如同一只丧家犬
Now I am an outcast, a pariah.
- 放她下来 - 记住 他想留个活口
- Put her down! - Remember, he wants her alive.
开火
Fire!
快点 开火
Come on, now. Fire!
我们追你追得好辛苦啊
You are an extremely difficult person to keep track of.
不用你帮忙
I don't need you.
但还是谢了
But thank you.
有什么话要带给迈克尔吗？
Any word with Michael?
- 别再跟着我了 - 我没跟着你
- Stop tracking me! - I'm not tracking you.
我要找到伊芙
I'm looking for Eve.
全天下我是最不可能知道 我女儿行踪的人
Well, I'm the very last person who could help you find my daughter.
赛琳 听我说 狼人又有动作了
Selene, listen to me. The Lycans are moving again.
不 这次不一样
No, this is different.
他们组织有方 他们有了新的领袖
They're organised. They have a new leader.
- 他叫马吕斯 - 我不愿再被牵扯到战争中
- His name is Marius. - I'm finished with this war.
可你躲不开的
Well, it's not finished with you.
他们本来应该把你杀死
They could have killed you...
但很明显他们的任务是活捉你
...but clearly their mission was to capture you.
你女儿的血极其珍贵
Your daughter's blood, it's a prize.
如果他们找到了她 如果她的血被他们利用…
And if they find her, if they use it...
马吕斯就天下无敌了
...Marius's power will be limitless.
那我还是希望她不被找到吧
Well, then I hope she remains lost.
替我给马吕斯带个话
I need you to deliver a message.
明白的话哼一声
Grunt if you understand.
告诉马吕斯
Tell your Marius,
要是他自以为能从我身上获得什么信息…
if he thinks he can extract information from me...
以便找到我女儿 那他打错算盘了
...to locate my daughter, he can't.
我不知道她在哪儿 我也不想知道
I don't know where she is, and I don't want to know.
马吕斯会找到你的
Marius will find you.
你了解自己要传达什么吗？
Do you understand your message?
这是什么？
What is it?
你之前见过吗？
Have you seen this before?
没有…
No...
但我们得把它弄出去
...but we need to get it out.
我们走
Let's go.
B岗一号 结束 有车开过来
Bravo one, over. Car approaching.
- 准许进入 - 关门
- Access cleared. - Close the gates.
(密码正确 允许进入中庭)
开始眼膜扫描
Commencing perimeter sweep.
先生 很荣幸终于可以迎接您回府
Privilege to welcome you home at last, sir.
塞米拉在她的私人房间等您
Semira awaits you in her private chambers.
塞米拉？
Semira?
卡西乌斯呢？
Where is Cassius?
当然 所有委员会成员都欢迎您回来 先生…
The entire council will greet you, of course, sir...
但塞米拉想单独见见您
...but Semira requests just a few moments.
你叫什么名字？
And your name is?
维尔加 先生
Varga, sir.
我会记住的
I shall try to remember it.
见机行事 因为这次悲…
...and act accordingly because of this tragic...
让我们单独待一会儿
Leave us.
亲爱的托马斯 咱们多久…
Darling Thomas. It has been...
- 没见了？- 几十年了
- ...how long? - Decades.
恭喜了
Congratulations.
听说你进了委员会
I gather you have a seat on the council.
我感到无比骄傲
I could not be more proud.
真可惜你的回归并不是因为有喜事相报
It's a shame that your return is not under more festive circumstances.
据说西支吸血鬼被彻底灭族了
It is said that the Western Coven was utterly destroyed.
是的 没错
Yes, it was.
你能活着逃出来真是老天庇佑
It's a blessing you escaped with your life.
很多都死在那里
Well, many did not.
我们已经牺牲了太多族人
There has been too much death among our people.
布达佩斯族一支就剩下这些骨灰盒了
These urns are all that remain of our Budapest Coven.
请节哀
Well, you have my condolences.
托马斯 我们要输了
We are losing the war, Thomas.
如果我们坐以待毙 不出五年 吸血鬼就都被灭族了
If we stay as we are, our species will be extinct within five years.
卡西乌斯同意你的观点吗？
Does Cassius share your view?
狼族重整旗鼓 整装待发 决意要将我们赶尽杀绝
The Lycans have regrouped, replenished, and are resolved to exterminate us.
当然 你在这儿很安全 东支防线牢固
Oh, surely, you're safe here. The Eastern Coven is a fortress.
今日不同往昔
We are no longer the coven you remember.
死神使者少得不能再少
We have fewer Death Dealers than ever before.
你身边这些都是新人吧
You seem to be surrounded by new cadets.
刚刚招进来的 不仅格斗经验欠缺 数量也不足以…
Raw recruits, neither combat-ready nor numerous enough...
抵御狼人大规模进攻
...to repel a large-scale Lycan attack.
狼人从未大举进攻
There has never been a large-scale Lycan attack.
至少没有一次协调有度的进攻
At least not a coordinated one.
马吕斯这号人物 在狼族史上倒是头一次出现
There has never been a Marius.
我虽不愿承认 但我这辈子头次…
Pains me to admit it, but for the first time in my life...
真正为我们的未来忧心不已
...I genuinely fear for our future.
那你有什么打算？
So, what is your plan?
塞米拉 你向来胸有成竹
Semira, you always have a plan.
你整这么一出 绝对是言在此而意在彼
This little mise-en-scene you're performing has a purpose.
我不擅长猜别人的心思
I am not a mind reader.
看在我这个老不死吸血鬼的份上 你就行行好…
Kindly do an old vampire the courtesy...
告诉我他为什么会来这里
...of telling him why he's been invited here.
赛琳
Selene.
快点 我们不能停下来
Come on. We need to keep moving.
还有比这里更近的安全屋
There are safe houses far closer than this.
我不是告诉过你了么 屋子都被他们毁了
I told you, they destroyed them.
现在情况不同了 快点
It's different now. Come on.
但你在她的死亡执行书上签过字
But you signed her death warrant.
当然了 我并不喜欢她
Of course. I despise her.
她杀了维克托 我是他的摄政者
She killed Viktor. I was his regent.
直到他遇见赛琳
Until he met Selene.
那你是想让她追杀马吕斯了？
So you want her to hunt Marius?
我想让她训练新人…
I want her to train our new recruits...
这样我们就有一百名死神使者 追杀马吕斯了
...so we have 100 Death Dealers hunting Marius.
我怀疑她会不会同意
I doubt she will agree.
她唯一担心的是自己的女儿
Her only concern is for her daughter.
伊芙 也就是那个混血儿
Eve, the hybrid.
不幸的是 这个可怜的女孩是半个狼人
Unfortunately, the poor girl is half Lycan.
虽说向狼人让步是吸血鬼的本性 但他们也不怕进化
It's a vampire's instinct to condescend to Lycans, but they're not afraid to evolve.
同时 我们居然为了"血统纯正" 这个狗屁理由…
Meanwhile, we stagnate from 1500 years...
整整一千五百年没有进化 真是没道理
...of this damned "species purity" nonsense.
讽刺的是 赛琳…
And the irony is that Selene...
可能是最纯种的吸血鬼了
...is probably the purest of us all.
这么说谣言都是真的？
So the rumour's true?
她身上流着柯文纳斯家族的血？
Her blood has elements of the Corvinus strain?
她很特别
She is special.
她让我儿子起死回生
She brought my son back from the dead.
- 她的血让他的心脏又跳了起来 - 不可能
- Her blood restarted his heart. - Impossible.
我亲眼所见 她救了我儿子的命
I witnessed it myself. She saved my son's life.
维克托和艾米莉亚
Viktor and Amelia.
并肩永生
Side by side for eternity.
如果我没记错的话 你非常喜欢艾米莉亚
You were very fond of Amelia, if I remember.
我需要你在此事上支持我
I need you to be my ally on this.
如果没有得到所有委员的邀请…
She won't risk coming here...
她不会冒险回来的
...unless she gets an invitation from the whole council.
而我无权就此事向委员会提出申请
And I could never solicit such a request.
卡西乌斯是个守旧派
Cassius is protective of the old ways.
我踏足委员会已经够让他不爽
He barely tolerates my seat on the council as it is.
可是托马斯 现在是非常时刻
But these are desperate times, Thomas.
所以你必须说服委员会邀请她
And that is why you must convince the council to invite her.
他们今晚就到
They arrive tonight.
黎明预警 一分钟后日出
Dawn alert. 60 seconds to sunrise.
马吕斯 各个部族的领袖们都已经到了…
Marius, the pack leaders have arrived...
我让他们在战情室等你
...and I told them to wait for you in the war room.
他们肯定吵成一锅粥了
They're fighting like dogs, no doubt.
- 我来处理 谢了 - 好的
- I'll handle it. Thank you. - All right.
- 继续 - 好的 好的
- Go on, then. - Right, right.
过来 过来
Come around, come around.
大家都听我说
No! Listen to me.
我们先把他们引进来 这就是我们的战术
We're gonna wedge them in. That's what we do.
从这边到那边 我们把他们引进来…
From this side and that side, we just wedge them in...
- 然后左右夹击 - 把他们引进来？
- ...and squeeze them out. - Wedge them in?
这就是你的计划？根本不可行
Is that your plan? It's not going to lead to anything.
- 他要生气了 - 闭嘴
- He's getting angry. - Shut up!
停下
Stop!
- 你是奴隶吗？- 不是
- Are you a slave? - No.
那就别表现得像个奴隶一样
Then don't behave like one.
看看这张地图
Look at this map.
你们都看到了什么？
What do you see?
你们有没有注意到
Do you see...
狼人争夺的 都是一些无关紧要的据点？
...Lycans fighting over scraps?
我是这么想的
I'll tell you what I see.
沃里尼亚地区
Volhynia.
诺德高地区 图林根地区
Nordgau. Thuringia.
狼人在以上地区取胜
The Lycan victories.
我看到吸血鬼横尸遍野
I see vampires dead.
整个地区的吸血鬼都被灭族
I see entire regions annihilated.
如果我们现在还内斗不止 是不会有什么出路的
But we will get no further if we fight amongst ourselves.
在摧毁他们最后的庇护区之前…
We must not rest...
我们不能停歇
...until we have destroyed their final sanctuary.
如果我们团结在一起 就能坚不可摧
Together, we are strong.
如果能得到那个混血女孩的血…
And when we have the blood of the hybrid girl...
我们将无往不胜
...we will be invincible.
格雷戈尔
Gregor.
只有你一人活着回来
You have returned alone.
- 我们受到伏击 - 赛琳呢？
- We were taken by surprise. - Where is Selene?
- 她没杀我 - 为什么？
- She spared me. - Why?
她让我替她转达一句话
To deliver a message.
她想让你知道 她的女儿已经永远消失了…
She wants you to know that her daughter is gone forever...
你永远都找不到她…
...that you can never find her...
因为连她自己都不知她被藏在何处
...because even Selene doesn't know where she's been hidden.
你信她的话吗？
Do you believe her?
你信吗？
我在她同伴的身上放了跟踪器
I put a tracer in her companion.
好吧…
Well...
你还算有点用处
...that means you're not completely incompetent.
站着别动
Try and stay still.
- 这是什么？- 一种子弹
- What is it? - It's some sort of bullet.
它能从你身上穿过去 根本不给你愈合的时间
It's burrowing through you faster than you can heal.
它自带动力
It's self-propelled.
其实我想告诉你们的是 狼人作战经验丰富
That's what I was trying to tell you. These Lycans are sophisticated.
我都不知道能否及时把子弹取出来
I don't know if I can remove it in time.
至少你可以装作一副让人安心的样子
Well, the least you can do is attempt to sound reassuring.
我会努力控制自己不把你杀死
I'm going to attempt not to kill you.
这样就够了
That will have to do.
你希望我们保护和赦免谁？
To whom do you want us to offer safe haven and amnesty?
死神使者赛琳
To Selene the Death Dealer.
就是那个杀死维克托的赛琳？
The same Selene who murdered Viktor?
卡西乌斯 这事儿你没必要提醒我
I need no reminder, Cassius, of what she has done.
先生 你真是无耻啊
Shame on you, sir.
别再向我提起她的名字
I will not hear her name spoken again.
卡西乌斯 你的愤怒我感同身受
Cassius, I share your outrage.
你中邪了吗？
Whatever has possessed you?
如果我们不采取果断行动
If we don't act decisively...
不出两星期 狼人就打到家门口了
...the war will be at your gate within a fortnight.
他们也就只能打到门口了
And that is precisely where it will remain.
狼人才不敢袭击我们这一族
No Lycan pack would dare to attack our coven.
我们的防御能力会让他们死无葬身之地
Our defences would rip them apart.
一般的狼人部族或许会这样…
An ordinary Lycan pack, perhaps...
但马吕斯这次召集的部队 实力超过以往任何一次…
...but Marius has gathered a force far more powerful than any...
胡扯
Unsubstantiated hyperbole.
你需要赛琳
You need Selene.
她卓尔不群 领导能力非凡 对狼人有着深刻的了解
Her prowess, her leadership, her intimate knowledge of Lycans.
而且她的格斗术无人能敌
And her combat skills are second to none.
他说得对 她是迄今为止最具杀伤力的死神使者
He's right, she is the most lethal Death Dealer we've ever had.
但她杀死过自己的族人
But she killed one of her own.
不仅仅是最有权力 最受尊崇的长老…
Not only the most powerful and respected of the Elders...
还是她的守护者 待她如同亲生女儿一样的人
...her protector, who loved her like his own daughter.
我们不信任她
She cannot be trusted.
她已经被定了罪
She has been judged.
或许我们还能再给她一次机会
Perhaps she can also be redeemed.
我虽不愿承认 但托马斯说得没错
It pains me to say it, but Thomas is right.
她是战场上最英勇的武士
No warrior has proved herself more in battle.
她会成为我们抵抗马吕斯的宝贵力量…
She would be invaluable in our fight against Marius...
甚至会成为我们取胜的关键因素
...perhaps even the pivotal element to secure our victory.
如果你们能找到她…
If she can be found...
而且并把她带回我们宝贵的营地…
...and sets foot within this precious coven...
塞米拉 她的行为…
...I will hold you, Semira, personally responsible...
- 将由你个人完全负责 - 当然
- ...for controlling her. - Of course.
侵略者 侵略者 侵略者
Intruder. Intruder. Intruder.
侵略者 侵略者
Intruder. Intruder.
谁派你来的？
Who sent you?
放下武器
Drop it.
你是怎么找到我们的？
How'd you find us?
剩下的安全屋不多
There are only a handful of safe houses left.
狼人反倒是帮了忙
The Lycans made it rather easy.
东族委员会让我带你回去
The council of the Eastern Coven sent me to bring you in.
- 是要审判我吗？- 不是
- For trial? - No.
为了你的安全 也为了我们的安全
For your safety, and ours.
你的话我可不敢信
You cannot expect me to believe that.
他们都曾在我的死刑执行书上签字
Every single one of them signed my death warrant.
- 情况变了 - 但吸血鬼不会变
- Times change. - Vampires do not.
这是你父亲写的
This is from your father.
真是他的吗？
Is it authentic?
他的印章 他的字迹
It's his seal, his handwriting.
委员会决定宽恕你 并且保证咱俩的安全
The council has offered you clemency and granted us both safe haven.
- 为什么？- 因为马吕斯
- Why? - Marius.
委员会真诚邀请你…
It is the council's humble request...
训练我们的部队 好打败马吕斯和他的人
...that you train us to defeat him and his army.
快走 快点啊
Move. Come on.
信号是这边传过来的
The signal's coming from this way.
听着 我知道你不愿意…
Look, I understand you're reluctant...
但作为委员会请来的客人 我们受到法律的保护
...but as guests of the council, we will be protected by law.
我父亲不会说谎 而且他绝无恶意
My father wouldn't lie, and he holds no grudge.
- 他也不是维克托的追随者 - 侵略者
- He had no love for Viktor, either. - Intruder.
- 狼人 - 侵略者
- Lycans. - Intruder.
- 我们得走了 - 你应该接受委员会的邀请
- We must leave. - You should accept the council's offer.
- 为了伊芙 - 伊芙不需要我的帮助
- For Eve. - Eve does not want my help.
我知道你想保护她 如果我们能打败马吕斯…
I know you want to protect her. And if we destroy Marius...
就等于是消除了对伊芙最大的威胁
...we destroy the greatest threat to her safety.
就是现在
Now.
马吕斯
Marius.
他们刚刚走
We just missed them.
别让我再听到"刚刚"这个词
I do not wish to hear the word "just" again.
要是找不到她 我们将一无所有
Either we have her or we have nothing.
明白吗？
Do you understand?
- 明白吗？- 明白
- Do you understand? - Yeah.
我方机动车驶入
Tango Charlie approaching.
没有发现异常
All clear.
周边安全
Perimeter secure.
- 欢迎 - 是吗？
- Welcome. - Am I?
营地内所有的资源和武器随你调遣…
Our coven's resources and weaponry are yours...
把这些新来的转变成 不会有辱你名声的死神使者
...to transform these raw recruits into Death Dealers worthy of your name.
维尔加负责协助你
Varga will be your right-hand man.
他知道我们的优势和劣势
He knows all our strengths and weaknesses.
他还是我们最多产的狼人杀手
He is also our most prolific Lycan killer...
一共有四十多个狼人死在他手下
...with over 40 confirmed kills.
- 我的荣幸 - 大卫 欢迎你
- It's an honour. - David, welcome.
- 谢谢 - 为了欢迎客人们平安到来…
- Thank you. - To mark the safe arrival of our guests...
我在冬日花园安排了小型舞会
...I've arranged a little soiree in the Winter Garden.
真没这个必要 谢谢你
There's really no need. Thank you.
说什么呢 及时行乐么
Nonsense. There's always a need to indulge in pleasure.
尤其是在战争时期…
In times of war...
族人更需要喜乐的气氛
...this coven needs moments to celebrate.
托马斯 大卫和赛琳的到来…
The arrival of Thomas, David and Selene...
这理由足以使我们庆祝一番
...is reason aplenty to rejoice.
为所有人干杯
To us all.
塞米拉 你能收留我们真是太好了 谢谢你
It's good of you to offer us sanctuary, Semira. Thank you.
乐意之至
It will be entirely my pleasure.
告诉我 她的血真的令你起死回生？
Tell me, is it true that her blood brought you back to life?
没错 是的
Yes, it is.
我这条命都是她的了
I owe her everything.
抱歉 我父亲让我过去
But, if you'll excuse me, my father requests my counsel.
托马斯一直都这么无趣
Thomas was always such a bore.
塞米拉显然对你很感兴趣
Well, Semira's certainly taken an interest in you.
只可惜这兴趣不是双向的
Well, the interest is certainly not mutual.
我们需要她的保护
We need her protection.
恰恰相反 我觉得我需要防着点她
On the contrary, I think I need protection from her.
瘟疫之战
The Battle of the Peste.
我们都以为那会是战争结束前的最后一搏…
We thought it would be the one to end the war...
终极一战…
...the final conflict...
结果到现在依然混战不止
...but here we are still.
我希望你明白
I hope you see...
我为了让委员会宽恕赛琳所付出的代价
...my bid for clemency for Selene for what it is.
你都把她女儿交易给了狼人…
Well, clemency is the least you can offer her...
为她求得委员会的宽恕 不是你最该做的吗？
...after bartering her daughter to the Lycans.
战争夺去我太多东西
I lost so much during this war.
我辜负了太多人 直到现在都无法释怀
Believe me, I am haunted still by all those I failed.
那你必须帮我保护好她
Well, then you must help me protect her.
她所失去的要远比我们想象得多
She has lost even more than we can imagine.
而且她对我来说很重要
And she's important to me.
如今马吕斯…
Marius is out there...
刚愎自用 根本不把咱们放在眼里
...reeking of canine insolence,
他预谋将我们灭族
plotting our downfall.
想要摧毁马吕斯 我们根本用不着赛琳
We do not need Selene to destroy him.
有我一人就足够了
I am more than capable.
不 维尔加 你只能算勉强够格
No, Varga, you are merely adequate.
幸运的是 为了求得生存
It's fortunate that we're not forced to rely on your skills...
我们不用被迫依靠你的本领
...for our survival.
而这个 我亲爱的…
That, my sweet...
然而和缺乏想象力的人做朋友…
...yet unimaginative bedfellow...
恰好是我的专长
...is my area of expertise.
- 我觉得你应该… - 千万别那么想 维尔加
- I think you should... - Don't think, Varga.
你会伤到自己的
You'll hurt yourself.
你还有其他方式可以证明自己的忠诚
There are other ways to prove your devotion.
各个击破…
Piece by delicate piece...
谜底最终会浮出水面
...the puzzle will fall into place.
没错…
Oh, yeah...
是的…
Yeah...
不要等狼人到了之后才行动
Don't aim where the Lycan is.
一定要抢在他们前面动手
Anticipate.
记住…
And remember...
狼人恢复原形时最容易受到攻击
...a Lycan is never more vulnerable than when he's in wolf form.
- 什么？- 没道理啊
- What? - That makes no sense.
一旦变回狼形 他们就无法使用武器…
In wolf form, they cannot use weapons...
他们的想法更加原始…
...and their thinking becomes much more primitive...
纯粹被杀戮的欲望支配
...driven only by bloodlust.
- 你杀过多少狼人？- 我没记过
- How many have you killed? - I don't keep track.
我要把狼人的速度加快百分之二十
I'm increasing Lycan speed by 20 percent.
请继续
Please continue.
我的部族探测过东族吸血鬼的营地…
My pack has probed the Eastern Coven's perimeter...
意图找到他们的防守弱区 却一无所获
...for weaknesses and there are none.
任何明取便会引发他们的一级防范…
And any direct assault would trigger the lockdown...
到时候营地就变得固若金汤
...which makes the coven impregnable.
即便我们还能有百分之九十的人打进去…
Even if we could break inside without losing 90 percent of our force...
- 他们还有撤退点… - 这个东西
- ...they have fallback positions... - This.
- 可以用来… - 准备好了吗？
- ...that can be... - Is this ready?
好了
Yeah.
一旦我们拿到混血儿的血…
When we have the hybrid's blood...
马上发动对东部营地的进攻
...we launch against the Eastern.
找到赛琳 就能找到她女儿
Find Selene, and we find her daughter.
这是我发明的
My own invention.
死神使者最先要学会的…
One of the first things a Death Dealer must learn...
就是如何在受限的空间内决斗
...is how to fight in a confined space.
当然 实际打斗中充满不确定性
Of course, the one thing this training session lacks...
这也是我们训练课程的不足之处
...is unpredictability.
也许你愿意帮我给我的学生们…
Perhaps you'll indulge me and give my students...
应该说是给你的学生们上一堂课
I should say your students a lesson...
专门讲格斗的突发状况
...in combat's unpredictability.
这样不仅咱俩能过过招 对他们的训练也是极其有益
It would not only honour us, but it would be invaluable to their training.
- 我不想… - 来吧
- I don't... - Please.
够了
That's enough.
都聚过来 我们让你们见识一下…
Gather round. We are going to school you...
真正的狼人勇士
...in the true nature of the Lycan warrior.
为了给你们上这堂课 我们尊贵的客人赛琳…
For the sake of this lesson, our esteemed guest Selene...
会作为死神使者 英勇守卫我们的据点…
...will play the role of Death Dealer bravely defending our fortress...
而我将扮作前来摧毁据点的…
...and I will take the role of Lycan villain...
狼族恶人
...here to destroy it.
女士优先
Ladies first.
好厉害
Impressive.
来吧
Come on.
来啊
今晚课程的主题是
Tonight's lesson:
打斗过程中 千万不要认为你的对手是正人君子
Do not trust your opponent to fight with honour.
他们是狼人 毫无底线可言
They are Lycan. They have none.
别动
Don't move.
龙葵
Nightshade.
一旦进入吸血鬼的细胞 通常来说都是致命的
Leeches into vampire cells, usually fatal.
但对于她这种体能比较好的吸血鬼 只会引发疼痛…
But for one with her strength, there will only be pain...
接着是四肢麻痹
...followed by paralysis.
我要杀了你
I'll kill you.
紫外线子弹
UV bullets.
你真以为我会原谅你杀了维克托？
Did you honestly think I would forgive you for killing Viktor?
维尔加 你军令在身
Varga, you have orders.
维尔加
Varga!
我根本不需要你来训练死神使者
I don't need you to train Death Dealers.
有维尔加训练就行了
I have Varga for that.
我若想统治这一族…
All that I need to rule this coven...
并阻止狼人的进攻 有你的血就足够了
...and end the march of the Lycans is your blood.
那尸体呢？
What about the bodies?
敲响警钟
Sound the alarm.
让委员会去找吧
Have the council find them.
尸体都是赛琳施暴的铁证
Conclusive evidence of the atrocity committed by Selene.
有人谋反
There's been a breach.
我们需要找到赛琳
We need to find Selene.
- 封锁这里 塞米拉的命令 - 让开
- Cordoned off. Semira's orders. - Step aside.
大卫
David.
走
Come.
营地里肯定还有其他的路
There's more than one way to move around this coven.
这些走道是艾米莉亚几百年前建造的
Amelia created these passageways centuries ago.
这条路通到哪儿？
Where does this lead?
私人房间 包括塞米拉的
To the private chambers, including Semira's.
他们到底对她做了什么？
What the hell have they done to her?
流尽身体之血
Machina sanguinem exhauri.
放血
Bloodletting.
塞米拉想得到赛琳最珍贵的东西
Semira wants Selene's most precious asset.
- 这样她必死无疑 - 是的 没错…
- This is going to kill her. - Eventually, yes...
但整个过程漫长而又痛苦
...but it will be agonisingly slow.
你看
Look.
这个东西是用来扩张动脉的
This is designed to open the arteries as wide as possible.
一旦不小心 我们就会伤害到她 而不是在帮她
If we're not very careful, we will do her more harm than good.
小心
Careful.
这是她的？
Is this hers?
是的
Yes.
赛琳只用这种武器
Selene uses only this particular weapon.
吸血鬼内部臭名昭著的叛徒
A known traitor within our walls.
这跟我预想的一模一样…
This is precisely what I foresaw...
你也向我保证会阻止这一切的发生
...and what you assured me you would prevent.
他们的命都算在你头上
Their blood is upon your hands.
- 先生 我尽力了… - 别跟我废话
- Sir, I did everything... - Do not speak to me.
我们对她不能有一丝仁慈
There can be no mercy.
天涯海角 你们也得给我把她追到
I want her hunted to the ends of the Earth.
我一定要找到她
It shall be done.
把她给我活捉回来
And I want her captured alive.
明白？
Is that understood?
明白
Perfectly.
- 我们没时间了 - 好的 带上她
- We're running out of time. - All right, take her.
你们必须北上 去遥远的北方
You must go north, far north.
瓦尔·道尔
Var Dohr.
不
No.
父子合伙叛国
Father and son united in treason.
你跟赛琳先走
Carry on with Selene.
我来对付他们
I'll deal with them.
快点
Come on.
走啊 快走
Go! Now!
不
No!
黎明预警 一分钟后日出
Dawn alert. 60 seconds to sunrise.
继续啊 你或选择被阳光灼烧 灰飞烟灭…
Go ahead. The sun will burn you to ashes out there...
或选择有尊严地死在这里
...or you can die with some grace in here.
他们不怕光
They can walk in the sun.
失了那么多血 你得补充体能
You need to feed. You've lost too much blood.
那个孩子… 因为他帮过你的孩子
That child... Because he helped that child of yours.
我的儿子死了 死了
My son is dead. Dead.
大卫
David.
带她走
Take her now.
你必须去北方 去找瓦尔·道尔
You must go north. Var Dohr.
走啊 赶紧走
Go! Now!
谢谢
Thank you.
很遗憾你失去了父亲
I'm very sorry that you lost your father.
他打了一场硬仗
He put up a valiant fight.
失去一个你从未真正了解的人 感觉怪怪的
It's strange to lose someone you feel like you never really knew.
我妈妈去世时就是这样 可…
I feel the same about my mother, but...
我对她毫无印象
I have almost no memory of her.
我对伊芙也是
And I of Eve.
我根本不希望她来到这个世界
I didn't want her.
我也不了解她
I didn't know her.
现在我也失去了她
And now I've lost her.
你为什么一直说失去她了呢？
Why do you insist on saying that you've lost her?
她让我保证永远不会找她…
She made me promise I would never look for her...
让我忘了自己有个女儿
...that I would never consider myself having a daughter.
她这么做是对的
And she was right.
我爱过的人都没什么好下场
Nothing good has come to anyone I love.
你是我的家人 是我唯一的牵挂
You're family, and you're all I have left.
那你真的有麻烦了
Well, then, you really are in trouble.
你需要休息一下
You need to rest.
赛琳明显是跟狼人结盟了
Selene's clearly in league with the Lycans.
叛变都是托马斯和大卫串通好的
Thomas and David were complicit in this treachery.
他们不怕阳光
They walked in the sun.
单单这一点就能证明他们跟狼人勾结到了一起
This alone is evidence of Lycan collusion.
我们必须在光荣史册上将赛琳除名
Selene must be wiped from the pages of our proud history.
亚力克西娅
Alexia.
- 我们要为死去的同胞复仇 - 请务必小心
- We shall avenge our fallen. - See to it that you do.
你用了多少龙葵？
How much nightshade did you use?
我之所以犯错 主要是考虑…
I thought it best to err on the side...
维尔加 关于"你是怎么考虑的"
Varga, what have we said...
我之前是怎么跟你说的？
...about you thinking?
毒药会扩散
The poison will dissipate.
我需要没有任何污染的血 现在就要
I need this blood untainted, and I need it now.
不能心急
It cannot be rushed.
凡事得慢漫来
It must run its course.
绝对是这辆车
It's definitely the car.
但不知道他们去了哪里
But no sign of where they went.
我们分开搜查
Spread out across the city.
哪个角落都不能放过
Search everywhere.
四号站台停靠的那辆列车 已经到达终点站了
The train at platform four terminates at this station.
北边
Northbound.
我的力量会超过…
I will be more powerful...
卡西乌斯…
...than Cassius...
以及东族任何一个吸血鬼
...than any vampire in this coven.
- 搜查有什么进展吗？- 赛琳和大卫往北边逃了
- What news of the search? - Selene and David are heading north.
- 想当然他们也会 - 大人？
- Of course they are. - Your Grace?
他们会去投靠唯一存留的支族…
They will run to the only remaining coven...
寻求庇护 瓦尔·道儿 北欧防线
...to afford them safe haven: Var Dohr, the Nordic fortress.
但瓦尔·道尔只是个传说
But Var Dohr is only a legend.
我才不会如此抬举北欧防线
I would not give it such an elevated status.
那儿冰天雪地 穷乡僻野 挤满了可悲 偏安的懦夫
It is a frigid, dreary outpost full of pathetic, peace-loving cowards.
听起来好像你去过那儿一样
You speak of it as if you have actually been there.
不然维克托错宠赛琳那些年 你以为我去哪儿了？
Where do you think I was when Viktor wasted years with Selene?
做好准备
Prepare yourself.
长路漫漫 你需要独自行动
The journey's long, and I need you to take it alone.
如果冒险出动一个班的死神使者
I must be certain the traitor's there...
把他们派到离我们那么远的地方
...before I risk sending a full squad of Death Dealers...
我必须确定叛徒是在那里
...so far from this coven.
你要额外小心
You need to be more careful.
你得温柔一点
You need to be more gentle.
- 找到赛琳了吗？- 找到了
- Have you found Selene? - Yes.
她逃往北欧支族了
She is headed for the Nordic Coven.
为此我付出了一切
I risk everything for this.
- 为了你 为了我们 - 我知道 亲爱的
- For you, for us. - I know, my love.
塞米拉日渐一日贪图权势
Semira grows more insane for power with each day.
我们必须阻止她
She must be stopped.
我每天担惊受怕
And every day, I fear more...
生怕我们暴露了 都不知她会做出什么事出来
...what she will do if we are discovered.
拿不到混血儿的血 我没办法攻击吸血鬼东部支族
I cannot attack the Eastern Coven without the blood of the hybrid.
他们力量太强 即便是我自己的部族也没把握
It's too strong, even for my horde.
赛琳…
Selene...
她决定着狼人的未来 也决定着吸血鬼的未来
She is the key to the futures of Lycans and vampires alike.
她是你的
You shall have her.
瓦尔·道尔部族就在山脊那边
Var Dohr is just beyond that ridge.
大家都哪儿去了？
Where is everyone?
都看着呢
Watching.
我们是来寻求庇护的…
We come seeking sanctuary...
不是来打架的
...not to fight.
那你们算是来对了地方
Then you've come to the right place.
我叫莉娜
My name is Lena.
跟我来
Follow me.
那是什么？
What was that?
障眼法
Some kind of trick.
你肯定就是赛琳了
You must be Selene.
伟大的死神使者 真的是为了和平而来？
Does the great Death Dealer truly come in peace?
- 是的 - 那他是谁？
- I do. - And what about this one?
他是大卫 托马斯的儿子
This is David, son of Thomas.
我已经好多年没见到他了
Who I haven't seen for many, many years.
千万别介意他们盯着你们看
You must excuse the attention.
我们支族很少有客人到访
Our coven doesn't receive many guests, by design.
我们顺从自己的意愿行事…
We do as we wish...
- 并不理会他人的想法 - 那狼人呢？
- ...not as others would have us do. - And what of the Lycans?
我们离得太远 他们压根不会在意我们…
We are too far removed for them to take notice...
即便有兴趣 他们也受不了这里的酷寒
...and even if they did, our climate is quite an obstacle to warm-bloods.
要是没有你母亲…
This coven wouldn't exist...
- 北欧支族早就不存在了 - 你知道我母亲？
- ...without your mother's grace. - You knew my mother?
吸血鬼界无人不知 孩子
All vampires do, my boy.
不 我母亲出身卑微 她生我的时候难产死了
No. My mother was low-born. She died giving birth to me.
骗你的 你迟早会发现
A falsehood, you will find,
这是为了隐蔽你的真实身份而编的谎话
designed to keep your true lineage safe.
- 那她还活着吗？- 不
- Is she still alive? - No.
她的死令所有吸血鬼沉恸不已
And her death was a terrible blow to our kind.
我们为她举办的哀悼仪式 整整持续了一个月
The mourning ceremony we held lasted for an entire month.
这样的荣耀通常只有出身高贵的…
Such an honour is usually reserved for a high-born...
- 大长老才能享受到 - 是的
- ...a Grand Elder. - Yes.
- 艾米莉亚 - 是的
- Amelia. - Yes.
我母亲怎么会是大长老…
How could a Grand Elder have been my mother...
而且居然没人告诉我？
...and I not been told?
我给你个东西
I have something for you.
这是你父亲最伟大的发明 里面灌了银水
Your father's greatest work, infused with silver.
狼人看到它便会退避三舍
The Lycans will cower from the very sight of it.
- 好美啊 - 托马斯知道总有一天…
- It's beautiful. - Thomas knew that one day...
你会被吸血鬼和狼人同时围攻…
...you would be beset by enemies on both sides...
他预想得没错
...and he was right.
大卫 这意味着你才是东部支族的合法继承人
David, this means that you are the rightful heir of the Eastern Coven.
你父母在这里…
Your mother and father spent many months...
安全地待了好几个月
...within the safety of these walls.
维克托起了疑心
Viktor grew suspicious.
然后你父亲在塞米拉和她的军队到来之前…
Then your father spirited you away...
把你送了出去
...before Semira arrived with her troops.
- 那我母亲呢？- 她回到了东部支族
- And what of my mother? - She returned to the Eastern Coven.
她眼睛里散发出来的光…
The light in her eyes...
别胡编她是什么殉道士了
Don't try and fabricate some kind of martyrdom for her.
你还是实实在在地对她的决定 做出评价
I prefer a more honest appraisal of her decision.
她为了自己那宝贵的委员会 抛弃了唯一的儿子
She abandoned her only son for the sake of her precious council.
- 拿着 - 大卫
- Take it. - David.
大卫
David.
艾米莉亚让我把这个交给他
Amelia asked me to give him this.
你需要什么？
What do you need?
什么也不要 我只想单独待会儿
Nothing. I just need to be left alone.
好的 我理解你的感受
Yes, I know the feeling.
那我父亲为什么不跟我说母亲的事？
Why didn't my father tell me about my mother?
我不是很了解你父亲…
I did not know your father well...
但我知道他最怕失去你
...but I know that his greatest fear was to lose you.
父母总是让孩子失望 好像每个家庭都是如此
It seems it's the curse of every parent to disappoint their child.
至少你会为自己的孩子而战 赛琳
At least you fought for your child, Selene.
是的 但我还是失去了她
Yes, and lost.
大卫 你血统纯正 是最合法的继承人
You have pure-blood heritage, David.
你母亲是位长老
Your mother was an Elder.
你父母这样保护你 肯定有他们自己的苦衷
Your parents kept you safe for a reason.
他们只有保护好你 将来你才能统领东部支族
They protected you so that one day you could lead.
你母亲留给你一件礼物
Your mother left you a gift.
你人真好 可我不喜欢珠宝
Oh, that's very kind of you, but I have no use for jewellery.
这枚戒指不是我所说的礼物
The ring is not the gift.
礼物蕴藏在戒指里 那便是你母亲对你的爱
It contains the gift: a mother's love.
她的一滴血
A single drop of her blood.
也许它会帮你做出决定
Maybe it'll help you decide.
你来得刚好
You're just in time.
- 过来 - 这里是什么地方？
- Come. - What is this?
- 瓦利萨 中间地带 - 她死了吗？
- Valissa, the in-between place. - Is she dead?
没有
No.
她…
She is...
正在进化
...becoming.
她服了毒药
She took a poison.
以便去到神圣世界
It allows her to visit the Sacred World.
她回来之后 会对这个世界产生有新的看法
When she returns, she will see this world with new eyes.
我不理解这怎么一回事
I don't understand what this is.
一直以来 我们都知道第二世界的存在
We have long known there is more than just this world.
我父亲第一次带我来这儿的时候…
When my father first brought me down here...
我跟你的反应一模一样…
...I felt as you do now...
但我后来多次去过神圣世界
...but I have since been to the Sacred World many times.
我看到过许多常人看不到的事物
My eyes see beyond the surface of so many things.
- 我看到过你很多次 - 比如说？
- I see much about you. - Such as?
我看到你爱上一个狼人 杀死一位吸血鬼长老…
I can see you've loved a Lycan, killed a vampire Elder...
- 生下一个… - 别说了
- ...and given birth... - Stop.
我看到了你失去女儿…
I see you have lost your daughter...
这件事在你内心深处 留下深深的伤痕…
...and how much pain this gives you deep inside...
然而你总是把痛苦深埋心底
...where you will always hide it.
她是个特别的孩子
She's a special child.
很多战争会因她而起…
Many battles will be fought...
因她而败
...and lost over her.
- 你还看到了什么？- 黑暗
- What else do you see? - Darkness.
无边无际 笼罩在所有人头上的黑暗
One that touches us all.
如果你想让她安全 就得继续前行…
If you want to keep her safe, you will need to go further...
突破自己作为一名勇士的极限
...than even a warrior of your renown has ever ventured before.
我看过太多战争…
I have seen so much war...
太多杀戮…
...so much killing.
我再也无法忍受
I cannot bear more.
你在这里感受到的和平都是真实的
The peace you will feel here is real.
它渗入你的肌肤 抚慰你的灵魂
It seeps into your skin and comforts your soul.
跟我说说神圣世界吧
Tell me about the Sacred World.
水流便是通道
The water is the path.
艾米莉亚
Amelia!
我将我们的儿子取名为大卫
I name our son David.
大卫
David.
总有一天你会明白
One day, you will understand.
真的抱歉
I'm so sorry.
狼人来了 快敲响警钟
Lycans! Sound the alarm!
关门
Close the doors!
快走
Move!
我刚说完和平 战争就跟着你来了
Just as I spoke of peace, war has followed you here.
保护好你自己
Protect your own.
我必须要找到大卫
I must find David.
- 我们得把你送走 - 不 狼人是我们引来的
- We have to get you away. - No. We led the Lycans here.
我们不能眼睁睁看着人们送死
We can't let these people die.
快跑啊
Run!
这边 兄弟们
This way, men.
去那边看看
Go around that side.
她在这儿
There she is.
你这个寄生虫
You parasite.
动手吧
Just do it.
马吕斯
Marius.
终于见到你了
At last.
右边
On your right!
我要的可不止这些
I expected more from you.
告诉我你女儿在哪儿
Tell me where your daughter is.
我不知道
I don't know.
赛琳 我只要她的血
Selene, all I want is her blood.
只有她能结束这场战争
Only she can end this war.
我向你保证 她不会被杀死
I give you my word she will not be killed.
你算老几？
What are you?
告诉他她在哪儿…
Tell him where she is...
所有杀戮就能永远结束了
...and all this butchery will be over forever.
我不知道
I don't know.
说谎
Lies.
他们已经死了
They've gone.
迈克尔
Michael.
- 我解救了你 - 看看这双眼睛
- I freed you. - Look at the eyes.
我是谁？你不知道我是谁？
Who I am? Do you not know who I am?
- 我的女儿 - 我不想看到你
- My daughter. - I don't want you.
别找我
Don't look for me.
她没说谎
She's telling the truth.
她确实不知道
She doesn't know.
我要做的都做完了
My time is done.
他们在撤退
They are retreating.
我快没时间了
I'm running out of time.
我们必须对东部支族发起进攻
We must strike against the Eastern Coven now.
你知道自己必须怎么做
You know what you must do.
水流便是通道
Water is the path.
赛琳
Selene.
请赞美…
Praise the day...
日暮时分
...when it ends.
请赞美…
Praise the ice...
承重的冰
...when it holds.
请赞美…
Praise the sword...
杀戮的宝剑
...when it kills.
请赞美…
Praise the life...
活过的生命
...that has lived.
是时候了
It's time.
权力
Power.
简单又极具诱惑
Such a seductively simple thing.
要么无所不有 要么一无所有
Either you have it all or you have nothing.
好神奇啊
How fascinating.
艾米莉亚…
Amelia...
水流便是通道
The water is the path.
你应该留在这儿 大卫
You should stay here, David.
你可以把这儿当做自己的家
This can be your home.
马吕斯朝东边去了
Marius is heading east.
现在什么都阻挡不住他
There's nothing stopping him now.
我的同胞四面受敌
And my people are beset with enemies on all sides.
我怎么能在此苟活…
How can I stay here and live...
- 任由他们死去？- 他们需要领袖
- ...while they die? - They need a leader.
大门处安全 眼膜扫描
Gate secure. Perimeter check.
想我了吗？
Miss me?
- 东门安全 - 西门安全
- East gate is clear. - West gate clear.
开始眼膜扫描
Commencing perimeter sweep.
允许进入
Access granted.
有什么消息吗？
What news do you bring?
大屠杀
A massacre.
狼人袭击了瓦尔·道尔据点
The Lycans attacked the fortress of Var Dohr.
狼人在北边
Lycans in the north.
北欧支族完全被他们打了个措手不及
The Nordic Coven was taken completely by surprise.
- 死了不少吸血鬼 - 赛琳也死了吗？
- Dozens of vampires have been killed. - Was Selene amongst them?
死了 死在马吕斯手下
Dead. Killed by Marius himself.
赛琳真是个煞星 走哪儿哪儿倒霉
Wherever Selene goes, trouble surely follows.
- 大卫呢？- 我不知道
- What of David? - I do not know.
真希望我能早来一会儿 说不定能帮上什么忙
I only wished I had arrived sooner. I might have helped in some way.
你已经帮了不少了
Well, you've helped in so many ways.
你完全达到了我对你的期待
You've done exactly as I hoped and planned, if not more.
看到没 信息就是力量
You see, information is power.
我可是满怀激情收集的信息
And I collect it with a passion.
谢谢你把马吕斯带去了北欧支族
Thank you for leading Marius to the Nordic Coven.
你的狼族爱人
Your Lycan lover...
马吕斯肯定为一时的胜利欢欣不已
...must be delighted with his momentary success.
你以为我不知道
You thought I didn't know.
蠢丫头
Foolish girl.
黎明预警 一分钟后日出
Dawn alert. 60 seconds to sunrise.
整个支族都被狼人灭掉了
The Lycan scourge destroyed an entire coven.
藏在安全墙后使他们优势大增
To hide behind these walls increases their advantage.
我们不能跟马吕斯来硬的
We cannot take the war to Marius.
那我们就这样藏在安全墙后…
Should we cower in the safety of these walls...
- 等着被他挨个灭掉？- 别说丧气话 塞米拉
- ...while he picks us off one by one? - Curb your insidious comments, Semira.
这支族已经延续了一千五百年
This coven has held for 15 centuries.
还能再延续好几个一千五百年
It will hold for 15 more.
虽然我能勉强接受你的能力…
I hoped you would show strength...
但我还是希望你拿出实力来
...though I was willing to settle for competence.
我之前想错了
I was wrong.
什么意思？
What is the meaning of this?
如果委员会太过孱弱 无法采取行动…
If this council is too weak to take action...
那我便有义务这么做
...it is my duty to do so.
你被废除委员会委员一职 即刻生效
You are relieved of your duties as council members effective immediately.
叛徒回来了
The traitor returns.
你傻了吧 居然还敢回来
Oh, you are a fool to show your face here.
塞米拉 我要你血债血偿
I will make you pay for what you've done, Semira.
我们说话这会儿 马吕斯和他的部队就在来的路上
Marius and his army are heading this way as we speak.
- 我回来是为了拯救我的子民 - 你的子民？
- I come to save my people. - Your people?
杀了他 杀了他
Kill him. Kill him.
你渴求成为自己这一族的保护者…
You aspire to be the protector of your bloodline...
然而你为了争权夺势 不惜杀害自己的同胞
...yet you kill your own kind in pursuit of power.
一切到此为止
It ends now.
我是大卫 大长老艾米莉亚的儿子
I am David, son of the great Elder Amelia.
我是东部支族的合法继承人
And I am the rightful heir to this coven.
艾米莉亚根本没有儿子
Amelia had no son.
她曾预见…
Well, she had the foresight...
会有人阻止我继承王位
...to know that my claim would be challenged.
请拿给委员会
For the council.
艾米莉亚
Amelia.
他是真正的继承人
His claim is true.
大卫是纯正血统的最后一脉
David is the last of the purebloods.
这并不重要 你寡不敌众 且装备不足
Irrelevant. You are outnumbered and outgunned.
维尔加 继续执行我的命令 杀了他
Varga, your orders still remain. Kill him.
- 我让你杀了他 - 不
- I said, "Kill him." - No.
你发誓效忠于我
You swore to serve me.
我发誓效忠于支族的首领
I swore to protect the leader of this house.
发现闯入者
Breach detected.
- 安全系统启动 - 是狼人 他们来了
- Security system engaged. - Lycans. They're here.
在委员会审判之前把她关起来
Lock her away until she can be judged by the council.
安全系统启动 发现闯入者 安全系统…
Security system engaged. Breach detected. Security system...
她想要的战争终于来了
She gets her damn war after all.
维尔加 再给你一次机会
Varga, you can still be forgiven.
把她的嘴也堵上
Gag her as well.
赶紧的 开车啊 开啊
Come on, move that truck. Move it.
把握好角度
Watch your angles!
我们走
Let's go!
别动
Hold your positions.
- 楼梯那儿 - 你身后
- On the staircase! - Behind you!
- 退后 - 撤退
- Fall back! - Retreat!
栏杆后面
Behind the balustrades!
杀光他们
Take them out!
- 快点 - 行动 行动 行动
- Come on! - Move, move, move!
行动
Move it!
该死
Fuck.
瞄准目标
Aim at the ready!
开火
Fire!
避开光照
Hide from the light!
跑啊
Run!
快走
Move!
开枪 开枪
Shoot, shoot!
不可能
Impossible.
你就死在我眼皮子底下
I saw you dead.
我来了
I'm here.
还带了后援
I brought backup.
他们人太多了
There are too many of them.
你已经死在我手里
I've already killed you.
马吕斯
Marius!
- 马吕斯 - 求你了
- Marius. - Please.
我希望你父亲能活着看到这一切
I wish your father was alive to see this.
他做梦都想不到 你成为支族领袖这件事…
His ridiculous dream of you ruling this coven...
会让你把命都搭上
...will be the very thing that kills you.
没打中
Missed.
有效果了
Oh, it worked.
我是你们的人
I'm one of you.
不 不 不
No! No! No!
你杀了迈克尔
You killed Michael.
而这是他唯一留下的东西
This is the last of him.
你是我的家人 是我唯一的牵挂
You're family, and you're all I have left.
你不知道我是谁吗？
Do you not know who I am?
你们的领袖已经死了
Your leader is dead.
带着你们的伤员 赶紧离开吧
Take your wounded. Leave.
快走
Leave!
在最黑暗的时刻 我们打了最光辉的一仗
We fought our greatest battle in our darkest hour.
吸血鬼和狼人几个世纪以来纷争不断…
After centuries of war between vampire and Lycan...
和平终于降临
...this may at last be a time of peace.
我们要再次照顾好伤员…
We must once again tend to our wounded...
纪念死去的战士
...honour our fallen.
最后剩下的两个部族必须团结一致 找回力量…
Our final two covens must find strength and unity...
才能浴火重生
...to heal and rise from the ashes.
我的旅途也算圆满了
My journey has now come full circle.
我曾沦为逃犯 如今被选为三大长老之一
Once an outcast, I am now one of three chosen Elders.
从亡命之徒到拥有至高无上的荣耀
From hunted to the highest honour.
我已经活了一千年
I have lived 1000 years.
也许我会再活一千年…
I may live 1000 more...
也许我明天就会死去
...or I may die tomorrow.
但我不再畏惧死亡…
But I no longer fear death...
因为我已死过一次
...for I have known it once already.
我得以重生…
I am reborn...
我已见证过神圣世界…
...and my eyes have been opened to the Sacred World...
看到过未来
...and to the promise of what is yet to be.
没有开始
There is no beginning.
也没有结束
There is no end.
只有过程
There is only becoming.